Timing: usotsuki
Translation: Puto
The Dictator Switch
All right, go for the handle!
Listen up! If you don't make it to third base, I'll make you regret it!
All right, I get it.
Play ball!
Strike!
Strike! Batter out! Change!
Nobita...
Out! Game and set!
They totally beat us!
They scored 18 runs! How is this possible?
And you call yourselves players?! You were so pathetic on the field!
Especially Nobita!
15 out of 18 runs they scored were your fault!
And We'd have scored five more runs if it weren't for your clumsiness!
You're a disaster! We lost 20 runs thanks to you!
That many?
As punishment, do 20 laps around the field!
Come on!
I'm too tired to run!
Besides, you were the pitcher...
What did you just say?!
If you don't run, I'll make you run!
Wait! Nobita, you...
Gian's pretty harsh.
Good luck, Nobita.
This is so frustrating!
Why does this always have to happen to me?
That's because you're a terrible player, Nobita-kun.
No way! Even you, Doraemon...
Come on! If you don't want it to happen again, let's go train!
No way.
Because Gian's the problem.
If only he wasn't around.
If Gian were to just disappear, I could live my life happy.
Why couldn't he just move out?
If that's what you think...
Then let's give it a try.
Dictator Switch
The Dictator Switch!
Dictator Switch? What's that?
A dictator in the future had this made.
A dictator?
The term dictator refers to someone who is an absolute ruler  invested with disproportionate powers...
and he singlehandedly controls the country,
And a dictator in the future used this switch...
...to get rid of anyone who opposed him or or stood in his way!
What do you mean they "?"
Obviously, they vanish into thin air, as if they did not even existed to begin with!
Did not even existed to begin with...?
Wha...!
The fly's gone!
See? Easy, isn't it?
With this, you can make anyone who bothers you disappear
and you'll be able to live in a happier world.
But...
...making someone disappear like that is kind of harsh...
Either way, I'll have to give it some thought and see what I'll do.
Right, right. Do that then.
Gian may be a pretty bad guy, but...
I can't just make the poor guy disappear like that...
He's got to have some positive quality...
I dunno...
He's a brute and a bully, but...
Nobita-kun...
Got you. Don't even think about trying to get away.
What do you want now?
What else? I want you to run the other 10 laps!
Ahh! Don't be so mean!
Wait, Nobita!
Leave me alone!
No way! I won't let you off this one!
There's nowhere left to run. Prepare yourself!
Gian, disappear!
He's gone!
He's really gone...
I did something really awful...
I erased Gian...
What's wrong, Nobita-san? You're kind of pale.
He's gone.
I... made Gian...
Gian? Who's that?
Who, you say? Gian! Takeshi Gōda!
The guy with the big body who sings really badly.
Doesn't sound familiar.
You really don't know him?
Teacher!
Gōda-kun?
Yes.
There's never been any Gōda-kun in my class.
But Gian...!
I've never had a student by that name.
B-But...
What are you talking about, Nobi-kun?
See?
No... No way...
Takeshi?
Yes. Takeshi Gōda-kun.
No, I don't have any kid by that name.
I only have a daughter.
Gian? Who are you talking about?
I'm talking about Gōda-kun...
You know him?
No, I don't know him either...
Gōda-kun?
Yeah! Takeshi Gōda!
Gian!
Never heard of him...
What's going on?
Nobody remembers Gian...
Nobita-san?
What?
Are you all right, Nobita-san?
Yeah, more or less.
You look tired.
You should probably take a hot bath, then go to bed.
I know!
Here, you can use this.
What's this?
It's a bath salt.
They're very relaxing and they smell really nice.
Thanks.
You're welcome. Rest well, all right?
See you tomorrow!
Yeah. See you tomorrow.
What now? He didn't just disappear, it's as if he never existed...
Nobita!
Don't "aah" me, you moron!
It's your fault we lost today!
So in a world without Gian, Suneo took his place?
It's your fault we lost 20 runs, Nobita!
And if you hadn't screwed up so much, we could've won 7 more runs!
This is unreal.
What are you on about?! As punishment, you have to run 25 laps around the field!
He's even worse than Gian!
Don't think you'll get away!
Geez! Suneo, disappear!
Hey...
Suneo?
I did it again...
No way...
It's not... It's not my fault...
I don't know anything!
I won't use it again.
I'll return the switch to Doraemon.
Ah, Nobita!
Nobita?
Guys...
Nobita!
It's your fault we lost today's game!
Yeah, yeah!
As punishment, do 20 laps around the field!
Yeah, start running!
Yeah, yeah! Hurry up and start running...
Enough! Leave me alone!
Or I'll make you disappear!
Seriously...
Everybody's the same...
Nobi-chan!
Sheesh! The entire day playing around, yet you still haven't done your homework, right?
Why do you always do the same thing?
Hey, are you listening to me?!
Enough!
Please, don't make me angry today!
Bring back the two you erased?
I beg you, Doraemon.
I didn't really want them to disappear.
Even then...
Please, I beg you...
It's impossible!
There's no going back!
You're the one who wanted to make Gian disappear, right?
Yeah, but...
Either way, there's nothing that can be done. You'll be better off if you just forget about them.
I can't just forget them...
What a terrible switch...
Whenever I feel trapped, I get tempted...
It's too dangerous to take it with me.
Why does everybody pick on me?
The entire day playing, yet your homework's not done yet, right?
It's your fault, Nobita! 20 laps around the field!
You klutz! It's your fault we lost!
You suck!
It's your fault!
Stop it! Stop it already!
Don't make me use the switch!
But wasn't this what you wanted, Nobita-kun?
It's all your fault.
Do... Doraemon? Even you?
Pay attention!
You're horrible, Nobita-san!
It's your fault!
Enough, Nobita!
It's all your fault!
Nobita-san...
What?!
Why's everybody blaming me?
Man... Everybody, anybody!
Just disappear!
It's kind of quiet...
Mom?
Hey! Doraemon!
There's nobody here...
It can't be... No way...
I'm sure everybody's on the field...
Right...
That's gotta be it...
Shizuka-chan?
Hey! Shizuka-chan!
It can't be... Even Shizuka-chan...
Shizuka-chan? If you're there, please answer!
Hello?
Hello?!
Anybody?
Is anybody there?!
Nobody...
There's really nobody...
What now? What have I done?!
I've erased every single human being in the entire world!!!
I've erased...
...the entire world!
Men don't cry, Nobita Nobi. What's done is done, can't be helped.
And thinking about it, my friends won't be able to pick on me anymore.
And Mom and the teacher won't be able to scold me anymore.
Right! Now I can do anything I want!
I'm the master of the Earth!
I'm a dictator!
Okay!
First I'll eat something good, to build up energy.
I'm full.
I can't eat as much as I thought...
Time to play!
I wanted this car so much...
It's so cool!
Being able to do whatever I want is really cool!
Now every toy in the world is mine.
Oh, it's broken.
Hey, Doraemon!
I should've left Doraemon so he could help me...
There's nothing on TV...
Since there's nobody...
As usual...
When I can do anything I want...
There's nothing I actually want to do.
I know!
I can get into all the attractions, and without having to get in line.
Everything... Everything's mine.
It's so dark everywhere...
That's right...
There's nobody around...
I think I'll sleep with the lights on.
Ah! A blackout!
Let's see... Who should I call to fix the blackout?
Oh, right...
No matter who I call...
...nobody's around to answer.
Nobi-chan, do your homework!
Nobita, don't screw up!
Nobita, you klutz!
Do 20 laps around the field!
Right, start running!
You look tired...
Right...
I'm so tired...
Shizuka-chan was right, this smells great...
And it feels so good...
This has to be a nightmare!
In the morning...
I'll see Shizuka-chan again...
Shizuka-chan...
Anybody...
I need some company, anybody will do!
Even Gian will do...
Somebody, please...
I can't... I can't live alone!
Do you understand it now, Nobita-kun?
Yeah, I get it.
If you make everyone who bothers you disappear...
...you'll end up completely alone.
I suppose.
I was wrong.
Then you regret what you did?
Doraemon!
Sorry for scaring you.
Doraemon!!!
I missed you so much!
I'm so sorry, I didn't mean to erase you!
It's all right, now you understand.
Actually, this Dictator Switch...
wasn't made to make a person into a dictator
but for people to understand why being a dictator is bad.
I see...
Please, get everything back to normal.
Let's do it!
Nobi-chan, look how you left the dining room?
Go clean it up!
Mom's angry as usual.
You better go clean it up.
Play!
All right! All right, all right, all right!
Hey! That's no good, keep your eyes on the ball!
One more time!
My mom bought it for me.
You'll have to lend it to me.
Look! The klutz is practicing!
If you screw up in the next game, I'll beat you up.
Gonna beat me up.
Thank you, Gian.
What's with Nobita...?
I wonder what happened...
This noisy neighborhood is so much fun!